[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "If you were wearing your commissioner hat, what would you read into what the FBI has done today?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "wearing", "your", "commissioner", "hat", ",", "what", "would", "you", "read", "into", "what", "the", "FBI", "has", "done", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Well, quite clearly that they have enough information to focus on these individuals as suspects, not just persons of interest, but suspects.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "quite", "clearly", "that", "they", "have", "enough", "information", "to", "focus", "on", "these", "individuals", "as", "suspects", ",", "not", "just", "persons", "of", "interest", ",", "but", "suspects", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Would that be your deduction?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "that", "be", "your", "deduction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "You can guarantee they know more, they have much more video than they're putting out to the public.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "guarantee", "they", "know", "more", ",", "they", "have", "much", "more", "video", "than", "they", "'re", "putting", "out", "to", "the", "public", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Is your gut feeling that these two suspects are still around or that they would have disappeared at fast as possible?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "your", "gut", "feeling", "that", "these", "two", "suspects", "are", "still", "around", "or", "that", "they", "would", "have", "disappeared", "at", "fast", "as", "possible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "I won't even speculate on that because it would be useless speculation at this stage of the game.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wo", "n't", "even", "speculate", "on", "that", "because", "it", "would", "be", "useless", "speculation", "at", "this", "stage", "of", "the", "game", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "So is it likely from your experience that people that go to that length of planning and preparing and executing, would they normally have some kind of escape route, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["So", "is", "it", "likely", "from", "your", "experience", "that", "people", "that", "go", "to", "that", "length", "of", "planning", "and", "preparing", "and", "executing", ",", "would", "they", "normally", "have", "some", "kind", "of", "escape", "route", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Well, it depends.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "depends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "What is your take on where we are with this investigation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "where", "we", "are", "with", "this", "investigation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think much credit should be given to the law enforcement generally.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "much", "credit", "should", "be", "given", "to", "the", "law", "enforcement", "generally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "When they release pictures and video like this, is it safe to assume that all their decks are in a row in the sense of clearly once this goes public, these two characters will know that they're on to them, will by then they have cleared everything with the ports and the airports and so on so if they try and make a run for it to get out of the country, they're ready for them?", "question_tokens": ["When", "they", "release", "pictures", "and", "video", "like", "this", ",", "is", "it", "safe", "to", "assume", "that", "all", "their", "decks", "are", "in", "a", "row", "in", "the", "sense", "of", "clearly", "once", "this", "goes", "public", ",", "these", "two", "characters", "will", "know", "that", "they", "'re", "on", "to", "them", ",", "will", "by", "then", "they", "have", "cleared", "everything", "with", "the", "ports", "and", "the", "airports", "and", "so", "on", "so", "if", "they", "try", "and", "make", "a", "run", "for", "it", "to", "get", "out", "of", "the", "country", ",", "they", "'re", "ready", "for", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "MD", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Yes, Piers, this is the reason that we didn't hear this before now, that premature leak yesterday may have impacted the investigation as they say, with unintended consequences.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Piers", ",", "this", "is", "the", "reason", "that", "we", "did", "n't", "hear", "this", "before", "now", ",", "that", "premature", "leak", "yesterday", "may", "have", "impacted", "the", "investigation", "as", "they", "say", ",", "with", "unintended", "consequences", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Do you think, as my other guests have implied tonight, that they have a lot more information they're not releasing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", ",", "as", "my", "other", "guests", "have", "implied", "tonight", ",", "that", "they", "have", "a", "lot", "more", "information", "they", "'re", "not", "releasing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Working on that, do you think the FBI again may have a better idea than we do just from what's released?", "question_tokens": ["Working", "on", "that", ",", "do", "you", "think", "the", "FBI", "again", "may", "have", "a", "better", "idea", "than", "we", "do", "just", "from", "what", "'s", "released", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "What you're seeing is the actual videos.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "you", "'re", "seeing", "is", "the", "actual", "videos", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Also, part of what they're looking to now do by pushing these images out, everybody who was in that area guaranteed is now checking their videos, checking their photos to see, did I actually catch these two guys on my video?", "question_tokens": ["Also", ",", "part", "of", "what", "they", "'re", "looking", "to", "now", "do", "by", "pushing", "these", "images", "out", ",", "everybody", "who", "was", "in", "that", "area", "guaranteed", "is", "now", "checking", "their", "videos", ",", "checking", "their", "photos", "to", "see", ",", "did", "I", "actually", "catch", "these", "two", "guys", "on", "my", "video", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Well, apparently they're being absolutely inundated both to their websites, also e-mails, calls, everything, and social media is erupting with information.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "apparently", "they", "'re", "being", "absolutely", "inundated", "both", "to", "their", "websites", ",", "also", "e-mails", ",", "calls", ",", "everything", ",", "and", "social", "media", "is", "erupting", "with", "information", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "What is his condition today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "his", "condition", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "He's still in critical condition.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "still", "in", "critical", "condition", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "I mean, do you think that if you hadn't been there to do what you did when you did it, that he may not be alive today?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "if", "you", "had", "n't", "been", "there", "to", "do", "what", "you", "did", "when", "you", "did", "it", ",", "that", "he", "may", "not", "be", "alive", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "EX", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "I don't want to speculate, but you know, I knew something was wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "speculate", ",", "but", "you", "know", ",", "I", "knew", "something", "was", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "And what has been your reaction to the release of the pictures by the FBI of the two suspects?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "has", "been", "your", "reaction", "to", "the", "release", "of", "the", "pictures", "by", "the", "FBI", "of", "the", "two", "suspects", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "You know, I don't -- I hope they get them, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "hope", "they", "get", "them", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "What do you make of the development today with the two suspects given that it clearly shows a team?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "development", "today", "with", "the", "two", "suspects", "given", "that", "it", "clearly", "shows", "a", "team", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Do we know any more about who is more likely to have done this, homegrown or a foreign, perhaps al Qaeda related cell?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "know", "any", "more", "about", "who", "is", "more", "likely", "to", "have", "done", "this", ",", "homegrown", "or", "a", "foreign", ",", "perhaps", "al", "Qaeda", "related", "cell", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "DT", ",", "IN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Well, the jury is still out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "jury", "is", "still", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", ":", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "IN", "JJ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "In other words, does the FBI know a bit more and perhaps believe it may be homegrown for that reason, or are they thinking perhaps no, this is looking more and more like al Qaeda?", "question_tokens": ["In", "other", "words", ",", "does", "the", "FBI", "know", "a", "bit", "more", "and", "perhaps", "believe", "it", "may", "be", "homegrown", "for", "that", "reason", ",", "or", "are", "they", "thinking", "perhaps", "no", ",", "this", "is", "looking", "more", "and", "more", "like", "al", "Qaeda", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "No, you know, Piers, I think they've been very deliberate about letting -- leaving all those options open, right, because what's really important to them is to find the individuals and once you've got them, you'll know -- for certain what the motivation was.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "think", "they", "'ve", "been", "very", "deliberate", "about", "letting", "--", "leaving", "all", "those", "options", "open", ",", "right", ",", "because", "what", "'s", "really", "important", "to", "them", "is", "to", "find", "the", "individuals", "and", "once", "you", "'ve", "got", "them", ",", "you", "'ll", "know", "--", "for", "certain", "what", "the", "motivation", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Is that what today is all about, that they need to have people coming on saying I know who these are?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "today", "is", "all", "about", ",", "that", "they", "need", "to", "have", "people", "coming", "on", "saying", "I", "know", "who", "these", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "You're absolutely right, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "absolutely", "right", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Jim Maxwell, looking at this device here, how easy is it for a would-be terrorist to bring this kind of thing on a backpack into a situation like this?", "question_tokens": ["Jim", "Maxwell", ",", "looking", "at", "this", "device", "here", ",", "how", "easy", "is", "it", "for", "a", "would-be", "terrorist", "to", "bring", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "on", "a", "backpack", "into", "a", "situation", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "It would be extremely easy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "extremely", "easy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim Maxwell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Is that how they would have done it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "how", "they", "would", "have", "done", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Well, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "The fact that they stayed around to see the explosions, what does that tell you about potentially the kind of construct of this device?", "question_tokens": ["The", "fact", "that", "they", "stayed", "around", "to", "see", "the", "explosions", ",", "what", "does", "that", "tell", "you", "about", "potentially", "the", "kind", "of", "construct", "of", "this", "device", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, it could go in several different directions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "could", "go", "in", "several", "different", "directions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Fran Townsend, in terms of the international element to this, if it is a foreign group related to al Qaeda or whatever, and they have either absconded or are trying to abscond the country, what are the wheels that go into motion there as far as national security?", "question_tokens": ["Fran", "Townsend", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "international", "element", "to", "this", ",", "if", "it", "is", "a", "foreign", "group", "related", "to", "al", "Qaeda", "or", "whatever", ",", "and", "they", "have", "either", "absconded", "or", "are", "trying", "to", "abscond", "the", "country", ",", "what", "are", "the", "wheels", "that", "go", "into", "motion", "there", "as", "far", "as", "national", "security", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "JJR", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "CC", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "EX", "IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fran Townsend"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "What kind of cooperation can the FBI expect from places like Pakistan?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "cooperation", "can", "the", "FBI", "expect", "from", "places", "like", "Pakistan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "They'll get cooperation.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'ll", "get", "cooperation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"], "LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "What does that tell you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "tell", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "It tells me that somebody had some practice here, and somebody cased the area.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "tells", "me", "that", "somebody", "had", "some", "practice", "here", ",", "and", "somebody", "cased", "the", "area", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "If you were running the FBI with this, how worried would you be that you may never track them down?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "running", "the", "FBI", "with", "this", ",", "how", "worried", "would", "you", "be", "that", "you", "may", "never", "track", "them", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I would be worried about it, but it was a great move today by putting their faces on television, as was said earlier by Fran.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "be", "worried", "about", "it", ",", "but", "it", "was", "a", "great", "move", "today", "by", "putting", "their", "faces", "on", "television", ",", "as", "was", "said", "earlier", "by", "Fran", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Lisa, first of all, how are you feeling?", "question_tokens": ["Lisa", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "how", "are", "you", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Doing fine.", "answer_tokens": ["Doing", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "What did you think was happening?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "was", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Oh, I was watching TV.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "was", "watching", "TV", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "In terms of the injuries that Lisa suffered, it's all from the glass, is it?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "the", "injuries", "that", "Lisa", "suffered", ",", "it", "'s", "all", "from", "the", "glass", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "She -- yeah, she has some scratches on her eyes.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "--", "yeah", ",", "she", "has", "some", "scratches", "on", "her", "eyes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lisa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Do you feel fortunate that your injuries aren't as bad as so many others?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "fortunate", "that", "your", "injuries", "are", "n't", "as", "bad", "as", "so", "many", "others", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I was just lucky.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "just", "lucky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Are any of the families allowed to go anywhere near it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "any", "of", "the", "families", "allowed", "to", "go", "anywhere", "near", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Last I heard, our uncle wasn't able to go to his house.", "answer_tokens": ["Last", "I", "heard", ",", "our", "uncle", "was", "n't", "able", "to", "go", "to", "his", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Boston"], "TIME": ["this last night"]}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "What is the state of play there now with all those different things?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "state", "of", "play", "there", "now", "with", "all", "those", "different", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Well, you know, talking about the blast first, Piers, and putting this in some context with respect to Boston, because you and I were talking about this last night.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "talking", "about", "the", "blast", "first", ",", "Piers", ",", "and", "putting", "this", "in", "some", "context", "with", "respect", "to", "Boston", ",", "because", "you", "and", "I", "were", "talking", "about", "this", "last", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "What was it like to be there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "to", "be", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "It was -- first of all, it was an honor to be able to be there, given the light of the unfortunate situation.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "it", "was", "an", "honor", "to", "be", "able", "to", "be", "there", ",", "given", "the", "light", "of", "the", "unfortunate", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130418pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "When you saw that breaking this afternoon, what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "that", "breaking", "this", "afternoon", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I'm just happy that they are finally getting somewhere.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "happy", "that", "they", "are", "finally", "getting", "somewhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this afternoon"]}}]